http://www.chilliworld.com/privacy-statement

Register
Log in
Wishlist
(0)
Shopping basket
(0)
You have no items in your shopping basket.
ChillWorld Privacy Statement
This privacy statements sets out the conditions under which you can expect the information we maintain about you to be treated.
ChilliWorld has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.chilliworld.com
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site.
This site contains links to other sites. ChilliWorld Limited are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products and services. We save customer billing and shipping addresses, first name, last name and email address for fulfilling the order. We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties.
If you would like us to delete your personal information please contact us and we will be happy to do so.
Registered users can opt in to receive periodic emails from Chilliworld regarding chilli related news and offers and they can opt out at any time from their account management page.
In addition, non-registered users can sign up to our newsletters following the links on our website.
Each newsletter email sent by ChillWorld will include an unsubscribe link for anyone who does not wish to receive further newsletters from us.
Product Reviews
Registered and non-registered users can leave product reviews. Please remember that information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control.
Payment
The site uses Paypal to collect payment. We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties. Payment is taken in full at the time of purchase.
Information
Sitemap
Delivery & Returns
Privacy Statement
About us
Contact us
Customer service
Search
Wait...
Copyright © 2020 ChilliWorld.com. All rights reserved.
